import 'package:takrorlash/data/model/question_model.dart';

List<QuestionModel> questionsList = [
  QuestionModel(question: "0 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'bir'),
  QuestionModel(question: "1 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'ikki'),
  QuestionModel(question: "2 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'uch'),
  QuestionModel(question: "3 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: "to'rt"),
  QuestionModel(question: "4 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'besh'),
  QuestionModel(question: "5 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'olti'),
  QuestionModel(question: "6 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'yetti'),
  QuestionModel(question: "7 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: 'sakkiz'),
  QuestionModel(question: "8 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: "to'qqiz"),
  QuestionModel(question: "9 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: "o'n"),
  QuestionModel(question: "10 dan keyin son? ", correctAnswer: "o'nbir"),
];